<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on CIST</title>
    <link>https://vantnprof.github.io/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on CIST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:18:38 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vantnprof.github.io/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://vantnprof.github.io/about/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:18:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vantnprof.github.io/about/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Education backgrounds 2023-current
Ph.D. student in the Electrical Engineering program at the University of Texas at San Antonio (UTSA), US.
2018-2022
B.S. Honor program in Computer Science at Vietnam National University, Ho Chi Minh City - University of Information Technology(VNUHCM-UIT).
Publications Trien Thai, T. Nguyen, Tuan Nguyen. 2022. Phương pháp xác định vị trí tàu biển gặp nạn (English title: Detecting the ship in distress based on optical satellite images and automatic identity system signal).</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="education-backgrounds">Education backgrounds</h2>
<hr>
<p><strong>2023-current</strong></p>
<p>Ph.D. student in the Electrical Engineering program at the University of Texas at San Antonio (UTSA), US.</p>
<p><strong>2018-2022</strong></p>
<p>B.S. Honor program in Computer Science at Vietnam National University, Ho Chi Minh City - University of Information Technology(VNUHCM-UIT).</p>
<h2 id="publications">Publications</h2>
<hr>
<p>Trien Thai, <strong>T. Nguyen</strong>, Tuan Nguyen. 2022. Phương pháp xác định vị trí tàu biển gặp nạn (English title: Detecting the ship in distress based on optical satellite images and automatic identity system signal). Submitted Oct 24, 2022</p>
<p>M. Tran, T. Pham, <strong>T. Nguyen</strong>, T. Do and T. N. Duc, “A robust framework for mathematical formula detection,” 2021 International Conference on Multimedia Analysis and Pattern Recognition (MAPR), 2021, pp. 1-6, doi: 10.1109/MAPR53640.2021.9585197.</p>
<h2 id="work-experiences">Work experiences</h2>
<hr>
<p><strong>2023-current</strong></p>
<p>Graduate research assisant (GRA) at University of Texas at San Antonio (UTSA).</p>
<p><strong>2022-2023</strong></p>
<p>AI research engineer at Viettel High Technology Industries Corporation (VHT), Vietnam.</p>
<h2 id="miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</h2>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>
<p>In Oct 2020, gained the consolation prize at the AI CAMERA INSPECTION CHALLENGE organized by The Training Center of Saigon Hi-tech Park (SHTP Training), Vietnam.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In 2019, Consolation prize in the Calculus at the National Mathematical Olympiad Competition organized by the Vietnam Mathematical Association.</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
